{
  "list": [
    {
      "question": "implicit",
      "answer": "含蓄的",
    },
    {
      "question": "concise",
      "answer": "簡潔的",
    },
    {
      "question": "fluent",
      "answer": "流利的",
    },
    {
      "question": "cogent",
      "answer": "有說服力",
    },
    {
      "question": "glossary",
      "answer": "詞彙表",
    },
    {
      "question": "dialect",
      "answer": "方言",
    },
    {
      "question": "clause",
      "answer": "條款",
    },
    {
      "question": "linguistics",
      "answer": "語言學",
    },
    {
      "question": "phonetics",
      "answer": "語音學",
    },
    {
      "question": "tense",
      "answer": "緊張的",
    },
    {
      "question": "genre",
      "answer": "文學流派",
    },
    {
      "question": "lyric",
      "answer": "歌詞",
    },
    {
      "question": "verse",
      "answer": "詩",
    },
    {
      "question": "fiction",
      "answer": "小說",
    },
    {
      "question": "byword",
      "answer": "諺語",
    },
    {
      "question": "fable",
      "answer": "傳說",
    },
    {
      "question": "term",
      "answer": "術語",
    },
    {
      "question": "maxim",
      "answer": "格言",
    },
    {
      "question": "satire",
      "answer": "諷刺",
    },
    {
      "question": "farce",
      "answer": "鬧劇",
    },
    {
      "question": "adage",
      "answer": "諺語",
    },
    {
      "question": "synopsis",
      "answer": "大綱",
    },
    {
      "question": "compile",
      "answer": "編輯",
    },
    {
      "question": "entitle",
      "answer": "取名",
    }
  ]
}
